control the controllable guys here's a
little assignment I want you to make a
list of all the things that are freaking
you out making you nervous or
distracting you before or during a
tournament here's some examples I don't
want to play this or that opponent cross
it off you can't control it I get super
annoyed when other matches are running
late cross it off can't control it I
feel a lot of pressure in my matches
that's something we can work on check
out the pressure tools video in the
description and head over to the
Terminator College to work on the mental
side I want to win too badly can't
control the win you got to focus on the
process if I make a blunder my game
drops and I get very negative that's
mistake tilt something you can work on
one of the lessons of the mental Edge
course there's a lot of humidity in the
room and the tables are very bouncy
can't control it cross it off all you
can do is adapt control the
controllables pool players cross off the
rest and go to work